<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://kennymiyasato.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://kennymiyasato.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-07T09:12:50-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://kennymiyasato.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Kenny Miyasato]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dash]]></title>
    <link href="http://kennymiyasato.github.io/blog/2015/04/07/dash/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-07T09:01:59-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://kennymiyasato.github.io/blog/2015/04/07/dash</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://kapeli.com/img/dash-256.png" title="Dash" alt="Dash" /></p>

<h1>Dash</h1>

<p>Today we’ll be talking about Dash and how it has helped me through my journey at Flatiron School.</p>

<h2>What is Dash?</h2>

<p>Here’s is a little excerpt from their <a href="https://kapeli.com/dash">website</a>:</p>

<blockquote><p>“Dash is an API Documentation Browser and Code Snippet Manager. Dash stores snippets of code and instantly searches offline documentation sets for 150+ APIs (for a full list, see below). You can even generate your own docsets or request docsets to be included.”</p></blockquote>

<p>It is basically an offline API documentation, instead of going through google or the ruby-doc.org you can just press -Control + H- on sublime and it will pull up any code you have questions about.</p>

<p>I have been using this little app for a little less than a week, but so far it has been such a time saver! I would have to pull up my browser, then go to google, then start searching for what I was looking for.</p>

<p>This app is great for people who want to start learning a new language, veterans who sometimes forget how to format code, people who do their coding offline, or people that want to save some keystrokes!</p>

<h2>Installation:</h2>

<ul>
<li>Just pull up the App Store</li>
<li>Search for Dash</li>
<li>Install it</li>
</ul>


<p>Some notes about the first time running Dash:
Go to the downloads window and start installing the languages you need, Dash comes with some documentation but sometimes your specific language may not be pre-downloaded.</p>

<p>I first found out about Dash during a lecture with Steven Nunez, I was amazed as to how fast he pulled up the Ruby documentation, I said to myself, I need to get that!</p>

<p>So far my journey with Dash and all its goodness has been great! Every single lab I do and need help on, I just pull up Dash and it will give me an example on how things should be formatted and structured.</p>

<p><img src="http://versioned.nameberry.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/abby-dash.jpg" title="Dash from Incredibles" alt="Dash" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Post on Octopress]]></title>
    <link href="http://kennymiyasato.github.io/blog/2015/04/05/my-first-post-on-octopress/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-05T16:33:36-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://kennymiyasato.github.io/blog/2015/04/05/my-first-post-on-octopress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>&ldquo;Hello, World.&rdquo;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
